<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Covid-19</string>
    <string name="loading_text" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">Loading...</string>
    <string name="web_view_loading_page" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">Loading the page...</string>
    <string name="prixa_title">You\'ll be redirected to</string>
    <string name="prixa_desc">The artificial intelligence system that Prixa.ai provides will detect COVID-19 symptoms that you may have.</string>
    <string name="prixa_footer1">All rights are fully delegated to Prixa.ai</string>
    <string name="home_header">Are you felling sick?</string>
    <string name="home_desc">If you feel sick with any of covid-19 symptoms, please call immediately for help.</string>
    <string name="home_call">Call Now</string>
    <string name="home_news_header">News</string>
    <string name="home_preventive_header">Prevention</string>
    <string name="home_preventive1">Avoid Close Contact</string>
    <string name="home_preventive2">Clean Your Hand Often</string>
    <string name="home_preventive3">Wear a Face Mask</string>
    <string name="home_test_header">Do your own test!</string>
    <string name="home_test_desc">Follow the instruction to do your own test</string>
    <string name="info_title">Information</string>
    <string name="info_desc2">Developed by</string>
    <string name="info_acknowledgement">Acknowledgement</string>
    <string name="info_ack1">Data Information from data.covid19.go.id</string>
    <string name="info_ack2">UI design from simantOo for Nickelfox (free use)</string>
    <string name="info_ack3">Image Illustration from freepik.com (free use)</string>
    <string name="info_term">Term and Condition</string>
    <string name="maps_title">Case per Province</string>
    <string name="stat_title">Statistic</string>
    <string name="stat_subtitle">Cases Summary</string>
    <string name="stat_positive">Positive</string>
    <string name="stat_death">Death</string>
    <string name="stat_cured">Cured</string>
    <string name="stat_monitoring">Monitoring</string>
    <string name="stat_patient">Patient</string>
    <string name="stat_cumulative_cases">Cumulative Cases</string>
    <string name="stat_updated_cases">Updated Cases</string>
    <string name="stat_condition_positive_cases">Condition Causes Positive Cases</string>
    <string name="stat_positive_symptom_cases">Positive Cases Symptom</string>
    <string name="stat_age_group_cases">Age Group</string>
    <string name="stat_sex_group_cases">Sex Group</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_cases">"Cases: "</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_death">"Death: "</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_cured">"Cured: "</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_treated">"Treated: "</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_subtitle">of all Indonesia cases</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_subtitle2">"Cases Based on: "</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_sex">"Sex: "</string>
    <string name="info_window_prov_age">"Age: "</string>
    <string name="prov_layout_search" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">Search Province...</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_stats">Statistic</string>
    <string name="menu_maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="menu_info">Information</string>

    <!--    PREVENTIVE STRING ASSET-->
    <string name="about">
        This application is not intended for anyone who makes this application as a benchmark against
        covid-19 information although all information in this application is downloaded from the Indonesia
        official covid-19 government website (covid19.go.id). But this application is intended for software developer
        enthusiast to explore our potential in developing an application which in this case is intended for a personal portfolio.
        If the user feels disadvantaged when using this application, all full responsibility is yours.
        But if you feels benefited, you can give some positive feedback on the contact button above. Surakarta, 2020
    </string>
    <string name="social_distancing">
        With social distancing, we reduce contact with each other to prevent COVID-19 spread. Conversely, if you turn out
        infected but not aware of it, so keeping away from the crowd will really help prevent the spread.\n\n
        So, if someone infected with this virus then accidentally coughs or sneezes without closing his mouth,
        then the droplet will fall on a nearby surface. When there are other people who are not infected holding
        the surface, then touches the mouth, nose or eyes without washing hands first, he has high infected risk.
        \n\nThis is what makes the transmission of this disease rise dramatically in a short time.
        Many people are not aware that they are infected, then go to various locations to meet friends
        and relatives. As a result, the spread of this virus is increasingly widespread.
    </string>
    <string name="social_distancing_citation">
        From: https://lifestyle.kompas.com/read/2020/03/16/143303720/social-distancing-efektif-cegah-penyebaran-corona-bagaimana-caranya?page=all
    </string>

    <string name="wash_hand">
        World Health Organization (WHO) recommends that everyone always wash their hands
        in order to prevent the spread of the corona virus COVID-19. Clean your hands regularly and thoroughly with soap
        and water or alcohol-based liquids.\n\nWash your hands with soap and water or use cleaning fluid
        alcohol-based can kill viruses that may be in your hands. Washing hands can get you
        stay healthy and prevent the spread of respiratory infections and diarrhea from one person to another.\n\nGerms can
        spread from other people or surfaces when you: \ n1. Touch your eyes, nose and mouth with hands
        not washed.\n2. Eat or prepare food and drinks with your hands not washed.\n3. Touch the surface
        or contaminated object.\n4. Flinches, coughs, or sneezes on the hands and then touches the hands
        other people or objects.
    </string>
    <string name="wash_hand_citation">
        From: https://tirto.id/cara-cuci-tangan-dengan-7-langkah-menurut-who-untuk-cegah-corona-eLyQ
    </string>

    <string name="wear_mask">
        Research from the University of Hong Kong and the University of Maryland found that masks
        simple blocking 100 percent of droplets and aerosols. The Guardian writes, countries that are
        has required their citizen wearing a face mask from the beginning shows a lower mortality rate than
        countries that don\'t enforce it.\n\nHowever, the big challenge is using masks only
        will work if most people use it. Analysis from the Food and Drug Administration (FDA)
        about the flu estimates, if 50 percent of the population uses masks, transmission of the virus can be reduced
        by half. Meanwhile, if 80 percent of the population uses masks, the virus can be lost.\n\nBecause
        that, various regions are currently adopting laws that require the use of masks in crowded places
        such as public transportation and shops.
    </string>
    <string name="wear_mask_citation">
        From: https://www.kompas.com/tren/read/2020/04/08/073100465/pandemi-virus-corona-dan-alasan-kenapa-kini-kita-semua-harus-pakai-masker-?page=all#page4
    </string>
    <string name="info_lang_title">Language</string>
    <string name="home_global_data">Global Cases</string>
    <string name="home_confirmed">Confirmed</string>
    <string name="home_death">Death</string>
    <string name="home_recovered">Recovered</string>
    <string name="home_donate_header">Donate now!</string>
    <string name="home_donate_desc">We need your help to help those who affected by this pandemic</string>
    <string name="donate_desc">Help those who affected COVID-19 pandemic with a donation through kitabisa.com platform</string>
    <string name="donate_footer1">All rights are fully delegated to KitaBisa.com</string>
    <string name="info_ack5">Health test based on Artificial Intelligent by prixa.ai</string>
    <string name="info_ack4">News data provided by newsapi.org</string>
    <string name="info_ack6">Donation platform from kitabisa.com</string>
    <string name="info_ack7">Global data COVID-19 provided by covid19.mathdro.id</string>
    <string name="info_ack8">Medical frontliner animation from Paulo Bañas on lottiefiles.com</string>

</resources>